Kael mss., 1939-2001 LMC 3004
Lilly Library
- II. Directors
  - Mazursky, Paul (cont.) (Box 55)
    - Willie and Phil., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 55)
    - Materials concerning Mazursky (Box 55)
  - Medak, Peter (Box 55)
    - Zorro, The Gay Blade., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 55)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 55)
  - Mekas, Aldolfas (Box 55)
    - Hallelujah the Hills., photographs, clippings (Box 55)
    - Clippings concerning other films and brother Jonas Mekas (Box 55)
  - Mekas, Jonas (Box 55)
    - Guns of the Trees., notes (Box 55)
    - Clippings concerning Mekas, (see also: Box 115) (Box 55)
  - Melville, Jean-Pierre (Box 55)
    - L'Aîné des Ferchaux (Magnet of Doom - U.S.)., photographs (Box 55)
    - Bob le flambeur (Fever Heat - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 55)
    - Les Enfants terribles (The Strange Ones - U.S.)., photographs, printed items, clippings (Box 55)
    - Le Samouraï., printed item, clippings (Box 55)
    - Materials concerning other films and Melville (Box 55)
  - Menges, Chris (Box 55)
    - A World Apart., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 55)
  - Menotti, Gian-Carlo (Box 55)
    - The Medium., photographs (Box 55)
  - Menshov, Vladimir (Box 55)
    - Moskva slezam ne verity (Moscow Does Not Believe in Tears - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 55)
  - Merchant, Ismail (Box 55)
    - The Courtesans of Bombay., photographs, clippings (Box 55)
  - Meredith, Burgess (Box 55)
    - The Man on the Eiffel Tower., photographs, clippings (Box 55)
    - Clippings concerning Meredith (Box 55)
  - Metter, Alan (Box 55)
    - Moving., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 55)
  - Meyer, Jean (Box 55)
    - Le Bourgeois gentilhomme (The Would-Be Gentleman - U.S.)., notes, printed item, photographs, clippings (Box 55)
  - Meyer, Nicholas (Box 55)
    - Star Trek: The Wrath of Khan., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 55)
    - Time After Time., publicity, clippings (Box 55)
    - Volunteers., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 55)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 55)
  - Meyer, Russ (Box 55)
    - The Immoral Mr. Teas., notes, publicity (Box 55)
    - Materials concerning other films and Meyer (Box 55)
  - Michel, André (Box 55)
    - La Sorcière (The Blonde Witch; The Sorceress - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 55)
  - Mikhalkov, Nikita (Box 55)
    - Oci ciornie (Dark Eyes - U.S.)., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 55)
    - Neskolko dney iz zhizni I.I. Oblomova (Oblomov - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 55)
    - Raba lyubvi (Slave of Love - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 55)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 55)
  - Miles, Christopher (Box 55)
    - Priest of Love., (2 folders) (Box 55)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 55)
  - Milestone, Lewis (Box 55)
    - All Quiet on the Western Front., publicity, clippings (Box 55)
    - Mutiny on the Bounty., clippings (Box 55)
    - Materials concerning other films and Milestone, (see also: Box 115) (Box 55)
  - Milius, John (Box 55)
    - Big Wednesday., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 55)
    - Conan the Barbarian., publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 55)
    - Dillinger., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 55)
    - Farewell to the King., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 55)
    - Red Dawn., (2 folders) (Box 55)
    - The Wind and the Lion., notes, clippings (Box 55)
    - Clippings concerning Milius (Box 55)
  - Millar, Gavin (Box 55)
    - Dreamchild., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 55)
  - Millar, Stuart (Box 55)
    - Rooster Cogburn., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 55)
  - Miller, Claude (Box 55)
    - Garde à vue., notes, clippings (Box 55)
  - Miller, George (George Miliotis), 1945- (Box 55)
    - Lorenzo's Oil., script (Box 55)
    - Mad Max., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 55)
    - Mad Max Beyond Thunderdome., (3 folders) (Box 55)
    - Mad Max 2 (The Road Warrior - U.S.)., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 55)
  - Miller, George (George Miliotis), 1945- (cont.) (Box 56)
    - Twilight Zone: The Movie (Segment 4)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 56)
    - The Witches of Eastwick., (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Miller, George (Trumbull), 1945- (Box 56)
    - The NeverEnding Story II: The Next Chapter., press kit, clippings (includes publicity for Box-Office Bunny, directed by Darrell Van Citters) (Box 56)
    - The Man from Snowy River., press release (Box 56)
  - Miller, Jonathan (Box 56)
    - Materials concerning various films and Miller, (see also: Box 115) (Box 56)
  - Miller, Robert Ellis (Box 56)
    - Reuben, Reuben., (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - Sweet November., notes, publicity (Box 56)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 56)
  - Minkoff, Rob (Box 56)
    - Roller Coaster Rabbit., press kit (Box 56)
    - Tummy Trouble (see: Johnston, Joe. Honey, I Shrunk the Kids) (Box 56)
  - Minnelli, Vincente (Box 56)
    - The Band Wagon., program, clippings (Box 56)
    - Cabin in the Sky., photographs, clippings (Box 56)
    - A Matter of Time., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 56)
    - The Pirate., photographs, clippings (Box 56)
    - The Sandpiper., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 56)
    - Materials concerning other films and Minnelli (Box 56)
  - Mizoguchi, Kenji (Box 56)
    - Ugetsu monogatari (Tales of Ugetsu - U.S.)., photographs, printed item, clippings (Box 56)
    - Materials concerning other films and Mizoguchi (Box 56)
  - Mizrahi, Moshé (Box 56)
    - Clippings concerning various films (Box 56)
  - Molinaro, Edouard (Box 56)
    - La cage aux folles., publicity, clippings (Box 56)
    - La cage aux folles II., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 56)
  - Moore, Michael (Box 56)
    - Roger & Me., (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Moore, Robert (Box 56)
    - Chapter Two., notes, clippings (Box 56)
    - Murder by Death., notes, clippings (Box 56)
  - Moore, Tom (Box 56)
    - 'Night, Mother., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 56)
  - Montaldo, Giuliano (Box 56)
    - Ad ogni costo (Grand Slam - U.S.)., notes (Box 56)
  - Moreau, Jeanne (Box 56)
    - L'Adolescente (The Adolescent - U.S.)., clippings (Box 56)
    - Lumière., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 56)
    - Materials concerning Moreau, (see also: Box 115) (Box 56)
  - Morrissey, Paul (Box 56)
    - Blood for Dracula (Andy Warhol's Dracula - U.S.)., clippings (Box 56)
    - Forty Deuce., publicity, clippings (Box 56)
    - Heat (aka Andy Warhol's Heat)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 56)
    - Mixed Blood., clippings (Box 56)
    - Trash (aka Andy Warhol's Trash)., notes, clippings (Box 56)
    - Woman in Revolt (aka Andy Warhol's Woman in Revolt)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 56)
    - Clippings concerning Morrissey (Box 56)
  - Morrissey, Paul and Andy Warhol (Box 56)
    - Chelsea Girls., press release, clippings (Box 56)
  - Morrissey, Paul and Antonio Margheriti (Box 56)
    - Flesh for Frankenstein (Andy Warhol's Frankenstein - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 56)
  - Mowbray, Malcolm (Box 56)
    - Don't Tell Her It's Me., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 56)
    - Out Cold., notes, press kit (2), clippings (Box 56)
    - A Private Function., publicity, clippings (Box 56)
  - Moyle, Allan (Box 56)
    - Times Square., press release, clippings (Box 56)
  - Mulligan, Robert (Box 56)
    - Bloodbrothers., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 56)
    - Clara's Heart., press kit, clippings (Box 56)
    - Inside Daisy Clover., notes, program, printed item, clippings (Box 56)
    - Same Time, Next Year., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 56)
    - The Stalking Moon., publicity, study guide, clippings (Box 56)
    - Summer of '42., notes, synopsis, clippings (Box 56)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 56)
    - Clippings concerning Mulligan (Box 56)
  - Munk, Andrzej (Box 56)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 56)
  - Murnau, F.W. (Box 56)
    - Der Letzte Mann (The Last Laugh - U.S.)., program, printed item, photographs (Box 56)
    - Nosferatu, eine Symphonie des Grauens., printed items, clippings (Box 56)
    - Sunrise: A Song of Two Humans., notes, program (Box 56)
  - Murnau, F.W. and Robert J. Flaherty (Box 56)
    - Tabu: A Story of the South Seas., notes, photographs (Box 56)
  - Murphy, Dudley (Box 56)
    - The Emperor Jones., photographs, clippings (Box 56)
  - Murphy, Eddie (Box 56)
    - Harlem Nights., notes, clippings (Box 56)
    - Materials concerning Murphy (Box 56)
  - Murray, Bill (Box 56)
    - Quick Change., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 56)
    - Clippings concerning Murray (Box 56)
  - Mutrux, Floyd (Box 56)
    - American Hot Wax., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 56)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 56)
  - Myers, Richard (Box 56)
    - Materials concerning Myers (Box 56)
  - Myerson, Alan (Box 56)
    - Steelyard Blues., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 56)
  - Narizzano, Silvio (Box 57)
    - Georgy Girl., publicity, clippings (Box 57)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 57)
  - Naruse, Mikio (Box 57)
    - Materials concerning various films and Naruse (Box 57)
  - Neame, Ronald (Box 57)
    - The Horses Mouth., photographs, clippings (Box 57)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 57)
  - Needham, Hal (Box 57)
    - The Cannonball Run., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 57)
    - Hooper., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 57)
  - Negulesco, Jean (Box 57)
    - The Mudlark., photographs, clippings (Box 57)
    - Titanic., (see: Box 115) (Box 57)
  - Nelson, Gary (Box 57)
    - The Black Hole., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 57)
    - Freaky Friday., notes, clippings (Box 57)
  - Nelson, Ralph (Box 57)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 57)
  - Neville, Edgar (Box 57)
    - Duende y misterio del flamenco (Flamenco - U.S.)., (see also: Box 115) (Box 57)
  - Newell, Mike (Box 57)
    - Amazing Grace and Chuck., (2 folders) (Box 57)
    - The Awakening., press kit, clippings (Box 57)
    - Dance With a Stranger., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 57)
    - The Good Father., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 57)
    - Into the West., script, clippings (Box 57)
  - Newman, Paul (Box 57)
    - The Effect of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the-Moon Marigolds., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 57)
    - Harry & Son., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 57)
    - Rachel, Rachel., publicity, clippings (Box 57)
    - Materials concerning other films and Newman (Box 57)
  - Niblo, Fred (Box 57)
    - Ben Hur., publicity (Box 57)
    - The Mysterious Lady., photographs (Box 57)
  - Nichetti, Maurizio (Box 57)
    - Ladri di saponette (The Icicle Thief - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 57)
  - Nichols, Dudley (Box 57)
    - Mourning Becomes Electra., (see also: Box 115) (Box 57)
  - Nichols, Mike (Box 57)
    - Biloxi Blues., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 57)
    - Carnal Knowledge., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 57)
    - Catch-22., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 57)
    - The Day of the Dolphin., (see also: Box 115) (Box 57)
    - The Fortune., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 57)
    - The Graduate., notes, press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 57)
    - Heartburn., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 57)
    - Postcards from the Edge., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 57)
    - Silkwood., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 57)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, notes, press release, publicity, printed item, clippings (Box 57)
    - Working Girl., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 57)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Nichols (Box 57)
  - Nicholson, Jack (Box 57)
    - Drive, He Said., publicity, clippings (Box 57)
    - Goin' South., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 57)
    - The Two Jakes., notes, clippings, script (Box 57)
    - Materials concerning Nicholson (Box 57)
  - Nierenberg, George T. (Box 57)
    - Say Amen, Somebody., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 57)
  - Nilsson, Leopoldo Torre (Box 57)
    - El ojo de la cerradura (The Eavesdropper - U.S.)., photographs (Box 57)
    - Piel de verano (Summerskin - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 57)
    - La Terraza (The Terrace - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 57)
    - Materials concerning other films and Nilsson (Box 57)
  - Nilsson, Rob (Box 58)
    - Heat and Sunlight., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 58)
    - Signal Seven (Signal 7 - U.S.)., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 58)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 58)
  - Nimoy, Leonard (Box 58)
    - The Good Mother., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 58)
    - Star Trek III: The Search for Spock., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 58)
    - Star Trek IV: The Voyage Home., notes, clippings (Box 58)
  - Norman, Leslie (Box 58)
    - The Night My Number Came Up., photographs (Box 58)
  - Norton, Bill L. (Box 58)
    - Cisco Pike., notes, press release, clippings (Box 58)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 58)
  - Noyce, Phillip (Box 58)
    - Newsfront., notes, program, press kit, clippings (Box 58)
  - Nugent, Elliott (Box 58)
    - Up in Arms., photographs (Box 58)
  - Nuñez, Victor (Box 58)
    - Clippings concerning various films (Box 58)
  - Nuytten, Bruno (Box 58)
    - Camille Claudel., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 58)
  - O'Bannon, Dan (Box 58)
    - The Return of the Living Dead., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 58)
  - O'Connor, Pat (Box 58)
    - Cal., press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 58)
    - January Man., (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - A Month in the Country., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 58)
    - Stars and Bars., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 58)
  - Odets, Clifford (Box 58)
    - None But the Lonely Heart., (see also: Box 115) (Box 58)
    - Clippings concerning Odets (Box 58)
  - O'Ferrall, George More (Box 58)
    - The Heart of the Matter., photographs, clippings (Box 58)
  - Oguri, Kôhei (Box 58)
    - Doro no kawa (Muddy River - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 58)
  - O'Horgan, Tom (Box 58)
    - Futz!, (see also: Box 115) (Box 58)
    - Clippings concerning other films and O'Horgan, (see also: Box 115) (Box 58)
  - Oliansky, Joel (Box 58)
    - The Competition., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 58)
  - Olivier, Laurence (Box 58)
    - The Chronicle History of King Henry the Fift with His Battell Fought at Agincourt in France (Henry the Fifth - U.S.)., notes, program, photographs, clippings (Box 58)
    - Hamlet., (see also: Box 115) (Box 58)
    - Richard III., notes, program, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 58)
    - Notes concerning Olivier (Box 58)
    - Photograph of Olivier, (see also: Box 115) (Box 58)
    - Clippings concerning Olivier, (2 folders) (see also: Box 115) (Box 58)
  - Olivier, Laurence and John Sichel (Box 58)
    - Three Sisters., notes, clippings (Box 58)
  - Olmi, Ermanno (Box 58)
    - I Fidanzati (The Fiancés - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 58)
    - Lunga Vita alla Signora! (Long Live the Lady! - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 58)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 58)
  - Ophüls, Marcel (Box 58)
    - Le Chagrin et la Pitié (The Sorrow and the Pity - U.S.)., notes, press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 58)
    - Hôtel Terminus., (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - The Memory of Justice., notes, clippings (Box 58)
    - A Sense of Loss., notes, program, clippings (Box 58)
    - Materials concerning other films and Ophüls (Box 58)
  - Ophüls, Max (Box 58)
    - Lola Montès., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 58)
    - Madame de... (The Earrings of Madame de... - U.S.)., notes, publicity, book jacket, photographs, printed items, clippings (Box 58)
    - La Ronde., (see also: Box 115) (Box 58)
    - Materials concerning other films and Ophüls (Box 58)
  - Oshima, Nagisa (Box 58)
    - Ai no corrida (In the Realm of the Senses - U.S.)., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 58)
    - Materials concerning other films and Oshima (Box 58)
  - O'Steen, Sam (Box 58)
    - Sparkle., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 58)
  - Oury, Gérard (Box 58)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 58)
  - Oz, Frank (Box 58)
    - Dirty Rotten Scoundrels., press kit, clippings (Box 58)
    - Little Shop of Horrors., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 58)
    - What about Bob?, publicity (Box 58)
  - Ozu, Yasujiro (Box 58)
    - Tokyo monogatari (Tokyo Story - U.S.)., notes, printed item, clippings (Box 58)
    - Materials concerning other films and Ozu (Box 58)
  - Pabst, Georg Wilhelm (Box 58)
    - Don Quichotte., photographs (Box 58)
    - Der Letzte Akt (The Last Ten Days - U.S.)., (see also: Box 115) (Box 58)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 58)
  - Pagnol, Marcel (Box 58)
    - Angèle., notes, clippings (Box 58)
    - La Femme du boulanger (The Baker's Wife - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 58)
    - La Fille du puisatier (The Well-Digger's Daughter - U.S.)., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 58)
    - Regain (Harvest - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 58)
    - Materials concerning other films and Pagnol, (see also: Box 115) (Box 58)
  - Pakula, Alan J. (Box 59)
    - All the President's Men., publicity, press kit (Box 59)
    - Comes a Horseman., publicity, clippings (Box 59)
    - Consenting Adults., press kit (Box 59)
    - Orphans., publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 59)
    - Presumed Innocent., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 59)
    - Rollover., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 59)
    - See You in the Morning., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 59)
    - Sophie's Choice., (3 folders) (Box 59)
    - Starting Over., notes, clippings (Box 59)
    - Materials concerning other films and Pakula (Box 59)
  - Palcy, Euzhan (Box 59)
    - A Dry White Season., publicity, photographs (Box 59)
  - Panama, Norman (Box 59)
    - I Will, I Will...For Now., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 59)
  - Papatakis, Nikos (Box 59)
    - Oi Voski (Thanos and Despina - U.S.)., press kit (Box 59)
  - Parker, Alan (Box 59)
    - Angel Heart., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 59)
    - Birdy., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 59)
    - Bugsy Malone., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 59)
    - Fame., notes, clippings (Box 59)
    - Midnight Express., notes, publicity, press kit, photographs, clippings (Box 59)
    - Mississippi Burning., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 59)
    - Pink Floyd The Wall., (for publicity see: Box 115) (Box 59)
    - Shoot the Moon., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 59)
    - Materials concerning Parker (Box 59)
  - Parrish, Robert (Box 59)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 59)
  - Pasolini, Pier Paolo (Box 59)
    - Accattone., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 59)
    - Salò o le 120 giornate di Sodoma (Salo, or The 120 Days of Sodom - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 59)
    - Teorema (Theorem - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 59)
    - Uccellacci e uccellini (The Hawks and the Sparrows - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 59)
    - Il Vangelo secondo Matteo (The Gospel According to St. Matthew - U.S.)., notes, program, clippings (Box 59)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 59)
    - Materials concerning Pasolini (Box 59)
  - Passer, Ivan (Box 59)
    - Ace Up My Sleeve (Crime and Passion - U.S.)., clippings (Box 59)
    - Born to Win., notes, clippings (Box 59)
    - Creator., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 59)
    - Cutter's Way., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 59)
    - Haunted Summer., press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 59)
    - Intimni osvetleni (Intimate Lighting - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 59)
    - Law and Disorder., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 59)
    - Silver Bears., notes, clippings (Box 59)
  - Patellière, Denys de la (Box 59)
    - Retour de manivelle (There's Always a Price Tag - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 59)
  - Patterson, Ray, Don Lusk and Alan Zaslove (Box 59)
    - GoBots: War of the Rock Lords., press kit (Box 59)
  - Pearce, Richard (Box 59)
    - Country., press kit, clippings (Box 59)
    - The Long Walk Home., notes, press kit, color slides, clippings (Box 59)
  - Pearson, Peter (Box 59)
    - Paperback Hero., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 59)
  - Peckinpah, Sam (Box 59)
    - The Ballad of Cable Hogue., (2 folders) (Box 59)
    - Bring Me the Head of Alfredo Garcia., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 59)
    - Convoy., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 59)
    - Cross of Iron., notes, clippings (Box 59)
  - Peckinpah, Sam (cont.) (Box 60)
    - The Getaway., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 60)
    - The Killer Elite., publicity, clippings (Box 60)
    - The Osterman Weekend., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 60)
    - Ride the High Country., notes, printed item, clippings (Box 60)
    - Straw Dogs., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 60)
    - The Wild Bunch., notes, publicity, printed item, clippings (Box 60)
    - Materials concerning other films and Peckinpah, (see also: Box 115) (Box 60)
  - Peerce, Larry (Box 60)
    - Ash Wednesday., publicity (Box 60)
  - Pelissier, Anthony (Box 60)
    - The Rocking Horse Winner., photographs, clippings (Box 60)
  - Penn, Arthur (Box 60)
    - Alice's Restaurant., (see also: Box 115) (Box 60)
    - Bonnie and Clyde., (see also: Box 115) (Box 60)
    - Dead of Winter., (2 folders) (Box 60)
    - Four Friends., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 60)
    - Little Big Man., (see also: Box 115) (Box 60)
    - The Missouri Breaks., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 60)
    - Night Moves., notes, clippings (Box 60)
    - Target., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 60)
    - Materials concerning other films, (see also: Box 115) (Box 60)
  - Penn, Leo (Box 60)
    - Judgment in Berlin., publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 60)
  - Pennebaker, D.A. (Box 60)
    - Don't Look Back., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 60)
    - Sweet Toronto., photographs (Box 60)
    - Ziggy Stardust and the Spiders from Mars., press kit (Box 60)
  - Peploe, Clare (Box 60)
    - High Season., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 60)
    - Couples and Robbers., notes (Box 60)
  - Peploe, Mark (Box 60)
    - Afraid of the Dark., notes (Box 60)
  - Perry, Frank (Box 60)
    - Mommie Dearest., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 60)
    - Play It As It Lays., publicity, clippings (Box 60)
  - Persky, Bill (Box 60)
    - Serial., script (Box 60)
  - Petersen, Wolfgang (Box 60)
    - Das Boot., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 60)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 60)
  - Petri, Elio (Box 60)
    - Indagine su un cittadino al di sopra di ogni sospetto (Investigation of a Citizen Above Suspicion - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 60)
    - Todo modo., photographs, clippings (Box 60)
    - Materials concerning other films and Petri (Box 60)
  - Petrie, Daniel (Box 60)
    - A Raisin in the Sun., clippings (Box 60)
  - Petrie, Donald (Box 60)
    - Opportunity Knocks., press kit, clippings (Box 60)
  - Petrovic, Aleksandar (Box 60)
    - Gruppenbild mit Dame (Group Portrait with a Lady - U.S.)., press kit, clippings (Box 60)
  - Pialat, Maurice (Box 60)
    - À nos amours (To Our Loves - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 60)
    - L'Enfance nue (Me; Naked Childhood - U.S.)., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 60)
    - Loulou., (2 folders) (Box 60)
    - Sous le soleil de Satan (Under the Sun of Satan - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 60)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 60)
  - Pierre, Roger and Jean-Marc Thibault (Box 60)
    - La Vie est belle (Life is Beautiful - U.S.)., photographs (Box 60)
  - Pierson, Frank (Box 60)
    - King of the Gypsies., (2 folders) (Box 60)